Dennis Thisner

076-513-3785 dthisner@pm.me github.com/dthisner

I am a Passionate people leader and accomplished project manager with Proven ability to quickly master new systems, build relationships, and synergies teams for optimal performance. Moving back to Sweden in 2024 to be closer to my family and friends. I have Significant, immersive experience in quality assurance and automation (8 and 7 years respectively), and extensive history in programming and testing with successful track record of delivering extraordinary results in a people-first, remote work culture, with a continuous focus on mentoring, coaching and collaboration.

Skills

- Quality control, Release Management
- Team Leadership, Mentoring & Coaching
- Risk Management, Process improvement
- Problem solving, Decision making
- JavaScript, Cypress, API testing, Golang
- Github Actions, Circle Cl
- AWS, GKE, Azure, Kubernetes, Docker
- Jira, Github bug tracking

Experience

APRIL 2024 - CURRENT

QA Manager / Rebtel, Stockholm

- Setting up the QA process from Design, to creating Test Cases to managing the releases
- Bringing QA into all the different departments as Growth, Data and Commercial
- Planning QA roadmap for creating Test Cases and Automation for our whole web & App

AUGUST 2021 - APRIL 2024

QA Manager / Plotly, Vancouver

- Mentoring and coaching team members to improve technical skills and leadership abilities.
- Lead the team to successfully delivering Dash Enterprise 5.0, 5.1, 5.2.
- Reduced the supported configurations from 21 to 14, saving about \$140 000 in cost.

JUNE 2021 - AUGUST 2021

Senior QA Engineer / Plotly, Vancouver

- Created a tool that reduced the seeding env time with over 40%.
- Created the testing process, defining what quality is and teaching it to the rest of the team.
- Setup Cypress successfully and run automatically in the CI and send out reports into Slack.

MAY 2020 - JUNE 2021

Senior QA Engineer / Apply Digital, Vancouver

- Successfully educated 4 manual testers to be promoted to QA Engineers.
- Adding native and web mobile E2E tests for iPhone and Android
- Lead QA effort for mobile game which received 2 awards. (Muse and NYX awards 2020)

JAN 2019 - MAY 2020

QA Engineer / Apply Digital, Vancouver

- Introducing and setting up Cypress and easy to follow "Get going with Cypress" tutorials
- Creating a streamlined and automated E2E setup and reducing the setup time with over 20%.
- Providing mentorship to junior project managers and product owners.

May 2016 - December 2018

QA Engineer / Cumul8, Vancouver

- Introducing and setting up Cypress and having it running in the CI.
- Schedule releases and manage the offshore team.
- Rebuilt the whole front-end CI builder, running 15% faster and easier to maintain.

Nov 2015 - May 2016

QA Specialist / Cumul8, Vancouver

- Created the QA testing process with test plans, test strategies for both mobile and web.
- Scheduled releases and setup Testing, Staging and Prod env.
- Pushed to get accurate and simulated customer data for the Prod env.

March 2015 - Nov 2015

QA Dev Support / United Front Games, Vancouver

- In charge of testing and deploying patches with a team of 8 testers.
- Figured out a way to reproduce issues using a dev environment that was pointing to the prod.
- Created documentation and tutorials to get new hires up to speed.

JAN 2015 - FEB 2015

Quality Assurance / Cumul8, Vancouver

- Implemented testing foundation with test plans and test strategies.
- Tested web and mobile applications.
- Thought the rest of the team about the testing process.

JAN 2014 - Nov 2014

Project Manager / Victory Square Games, Vancouver

- Planned and managed a team of 8 to successfully deliver 4 games to the Microsoft game store
- Successfully helped writing 2 proposal to get government funding
- Reported risks and progress to CEO, angel investors and Microsoft.

Education

JANUARY 2013 - DECEMBER 2013

Entertainment Business Management / VFS, Vancouver

An intensive course where I was taught about how the business side works within the entertainment industry, everything from being a great leader, a producer, event manager, and a project manager. Worked on several projects to learn hands on experience with being a manager.

Courses / Certifications

- React 18 Course 2024 Oct 2024
- Mobile Automation with WIO Jul 2024
- Testing Javascript May 2022
- Udemy React with Redux March 2021
- Udemy React JS and Redux Aug 2020
- Udemy Selenium WebDriver Jan 2019
- Udemy Web Dev bootcamp April 2018
- Udemy Learn How To Code: Golang Feb 2017

Interests and hobbies

Skiing, renovation, gardening, board games, Geocaching, archery, painting, carving & playing guitar.

References available upon request